export const solutions = [
      {
        SN: "1",
        problem: "ENGINE FAILS TO ROTATE WHEN ATTEMPTING TO START",
        solution: "1: Battery terminal connections loose or corroded.<br>2: Battery discharged or faulty.<br>3: Broken, loose, or disconnected wiring in the starting circuit.<br>4: Defective starter solenoid or switch.<br>5: Defective starter motor.<br>6: Starter pinion or flywheel/drive plate ring gear teeth loose or broken.<br>7: Engine earth strap broken or disconnected.",
        options:{
          yes: 'Yes',
          no: 'No'
        }
      },
      {
        SN: "2",
        problem: "ENGINE ROTATES, BUT WILL NOT START",
        solution: "1: Fuel tank empty.<br>2: Battery discharged (engine rotates slowly).<br>3: Battery terminal connections loose or corroded.<br>4: Ignition components damp or damaged.<br>5: Broken, loose, or disconnected wiring in the ignition circuit.<br>6: Worn, faulty, or incorrectly-gapped spark plugs.<br>7: Faulty choke or carburetor.<br>8: Fuel injection system fault.<br>9: Major mechanical failure (e.g. broken timing chain).",
        options:{
          yes: 'Yes',
          no: 'No'
        }
      },
      {
        SN: "3",
        problem: "ENGINE FAILS TO START WHEN COLD",
        solution: "1: Battery discharged.<br>2: Battery terminal connections loose or corroded.<br>3: Worn, faulty, or incorrectly-gapped spark plugs.<br>4: Faulty choke or carburetor.<br>5: Fuel injection system fault.<br>6: Other ignition system fault.<br>7: Low cylinder compressions.",
        options:{
          yes: 'Yes',
          no: 'No'
        }
      },
      {
        SN: "4",
        problem: "ENGINE FAILS TO START WHEN HOT",
        solution: "1: Air filter element dirty or clogged.<br>2: Faulty choke or carburetor.<br>3: Fuel injection system fault.<br>4: Low cylinder compressions.",
        options:{
          yes: 'Yes',
          no: 'No'
        }
      },
      {
        SN: "5",
        problem: "START MOTOR NOISY OR EXCESSIVELY ROUGH IN ENGAGEMENT",
        solution: "1: Starter pinion or flywheel/drive plate ring gear teeth loose or broken.<br>2: Starter motor mounting bolts loose or missing.<br>3: Starter motor internal components worn or damaged.",
        options:{
          yes: 'Yes',
          no: 'No'
        }
      },
      {
        SN: "6",
        problem: "ENGINE HESITATES ON ACCELERATION",
        solution: "1: Worn, faulty, or incorrectly-gapped spark plugs.<br>2: Vacuum leak at the carburetor, throttle body, inlet manifold, or associated hoses.<br>3: Faulty carburetor.<br>4: Fuel injection system fault.",
        options:{
          yes: 'Yes',
          no: 'No'
        }
      },
      {
        SN: "7",
        problem: "ENGINE STALLS",
        solution: "1: Vacuum leak at the carburetor, throttle body, inlet manifold, or associated hoses.<br>2: Fuel filter choked.<br>3: Fuel pump faulty or delivery pressure low.<br>4: Fuel tank vent blocked or fuel pipes restricted.<br>5: Faulty carburetor.<br>6: Fuel injection system fault.",
        options:{
          yes: 'Yes',
          no: 'No'
        }
      },
      {
        SN: "8",
        problem: "ENGINE LACKS POWER",
        solution: "1: Timing belt incorrectly fitted or tensioned.<br>2: Fuel filter choked.<br>3: Fuel pump faulty or delivery pressure low.<br>4: Uneven or low cylinder compressions.<br>5: Worn, faulty, or incorrectly-gapped spark plugs.<br>6: Vacuum leak at the carburetor, throttle body, inlet manifold, or associated hoses.<br>7: Faulty carburetor.<br>8: Fuel injection system fault.<br>9: Brakes binding.<br>10: Clutch slipping.",
        options:{
          yes: 'Yes',
          no: 'No'
        }
      },
      {
        SN: "9",
        problem: "ENGINE BACKFIRES",
        solution: "1: Timing belt incorrectly fitted or tensioned.<br>2: Vacuum leak at the carburetor, throttle body, inlet manifold, or associated hoses.<br>3: Faulty carburetor.<br>4: Fuel injection system fault.",
        options:{
          yes: 'Yes',
          no: 'No'
        }
      },
      {
        SN: "10",
        problem: "ENGINE STARTS, BUT STOPS IMMEDIATELY",
        solution: "1: Loose or faulty electrical connections in the ignition circuit.<br>2: Vacuum leak at the carburetor, throttle body, or inlet manifold.<br>3: Faulty carburetor.<br>4: Fuel injection system fault.",
        options:{
          yes: 'Yes',
          no: 'No'
        }
      },
      {
        SN: "11",
        problem: "ENGINE IDLES ERRATICALLY",
        solution: "1: Incorrectly-adjusted idle speed.<br>2: Air filter element clogged.<br>3: Vacuum leak at the carburetor, throttle body, inlet manifold, or associated hoses.<br>4: Worn, faulty, or incorrectly-gapped spark plugs.<br>5: Uneven or low cylinder compressions.<br>6: Camshaft lobes worn.<br>7: Timing belt incorrectly tensioned.<br>8: Faulty carburetor.<br>9: Fuel injection system fault.",
        options:{
          yes: 'Yes',
          no: 'No'
        }
      },
      {
        SN: "12",
        problem: "ENGINE MISFIRES AT IDLE SPEED",
        solution: "1: Worn, faulty, or incorrectly-gapped spark plugs.<br>2: Faulty spark plug HT leads.<br>3: Vacuum leak at the carburetor, throttle body, inlet manifold, or associated hoses.<br>4: Faulty carburetor.<br>5: Fuel injection system fault.<br>6: Distributor cap cracked or tracking internally.<br>7: Uneven or low cylinder compressions.<br>8: Disconnected, leaking, or perished crankcase ventilation hoses.",
        options:{
          yes: 'Yes',
          no: 'No'
        }
      },
      {
        SN: "13",
        problem: "ENGINE MISFIRES THROUGHOUT THE DRIVING SPEED RANGE",
        solution: "1: Fuel filter choked.<br>2: Fuel pump faulty or delivery pressure low.<br>3: Fuel tank vent blocked or fuel pipes restricted.<br>4: Vacuum leak at the carburetor, throttle body, inlet manifold, or associated hoses.<br>5: Worn, faulty, or incorrectly-gapped spark plugs.<br>6: Faulty spark plug HT leads.<br>7: Distributor cap cracked or tracking internally.<br>8: Faulty ignition coil.<br>9: Uneven or low cylinder compressions.<br>10: Faulty carburetor.<br>11: Fuel injection system fault.",
        options:{
          yes: 'Yes',
          no: 'No'
        }
      },
      {
        SN: "14",
        problem: "OIL PRESSURE WARNING LIGHT ILLUMINATED WITH ENGINE RUNNING",
        solution: "1: Faulty oil pressure sensor.<br>2: Low oil level or incorrect oil grade.<br>3: Worn engine bearings and/or oil pump.<br>4: Excessively high engine operating temperature.<br>5: Oil pressure relief valve defective.<br>6: Oil pick-up strainer clogged.",
        options:{
          yes: 'Yes',
          no: 'No'
        }
      },
      {
        SN: "15",
        problem: "ENGINE RUNS-ON AFTER SWITCHING OFF",
        solution: "1: Excessive carbon build-up in engine.<br>2: Excessively high engine operating temperature.",
        options:{
          yes: 'Yes',
          no: 'No'
        }
      },
      {
        SN: "16",
        problem: "ENGINE NOISES PRE-IGNITION (PINKING) OR KNOCKING DURING ACCELERATION OR UNDER LOAD",
        solution: "1: Ignition timing incorrect/ignition system fault.<br>2: Incorrect grade of spark plug.<br>3: Incorrect grade of fuel.<br>4: Vacuum leak at carburetor, throttle body, inlet manifold, or associated hoses.<br>5: Excessive carbon build-up in engine.<br>6: Faulty carburetor.<br>7: Fuel injection system fault.",
        options:{
          yes: 'Yes',
          no: 'No'
        }
      },
      {
        SN: "17",
        problem: "WHISTLING OR WHEEZING NOISES",
        solution: "1: Leaking inlet manifold or throttle body gasket.<br>2: Leaking exhaust manifold gasket.<br>3: Leaking vacuum hose.<br>4: Blowing cylinder head gasket.",
        options:{
          yes: 'Yes',
          no: 'No'
        }
      },
      {
        SN: "18",
        problem: "TAPPING OR RATTLING NOISES",
        solution: "1: Worn valve gear or camshaft.<br>2: Incorrect valve clearances.<br>3: Ancillary component fault (water pump, alternator, etc.).",
        options:{
          yes: 'Yes',
          no: 'No'
        }
      },
      {
        SN: "19",
        problem: "KNOCKING OR THUMPING NOISES",
        solution: "1: Worn big-end bearings.<br>2: Worn main bearings.<br>3: Piston slap.<br>4: Ancillary component fault (water pump, alternator, etc.).",
        options:{
          yes: 'Yes',
          no: 'No'
        }
      }
    ];

    export const Mechanics = [
      {
        SN: 'FC',
        StateName:'Abuja',
        MechanicName:' ',
        MechanicNumber:'0913608965',
      },
      {
        SN:'AB',
        StateName:'Abia',
        MechanicName:'',
        MechanicNumber:'0913608965',
      },
      {
        SN:'AD',
        StateName:'Adamawa',
        MechanicName:'',
        MechanicNumber:'0913608965',
      },
      {
        SN:'AK',
        StateName:'Akwa Ibom',
        MechanicName:'',
        MechanicNumber:'0913608965',
      },
      {
        SN:'AN',
        StateName:'Anambra',
        MechanicName:'',
        MechanicNumber:'0913608965',
      },
      {
        SN:'BA',
        StateName:'Bauchi',
        MechanicName:'',
        MechanicNumber:'0913608965',
      },
      {
        SN:'BY',
        StateName:'Bayelsa',
        MechanicName:'',
        MechanicNumber:'0913608965',
      },
      {
        SN:'BE',
        StateName:'Benue',
        MechanicName:'',
        MechanicNumber:'0913608965',
      },
      {
        SN:'BO',
        StateName:'Borno',
        MechanicName:'',
        MechanicNumber:'0913608965',
      },
      {
        SN:'CR',
        StateName:'Cross River',
        MechanicName:'',
        MechanicNumber:'0913608965',
      },
      {
        SN:'DE',
        StateName:'Delta',
        MechanicName:'',
        MechanicNumber:'0913608965',
      },
      {
        SN:'EB',
        StateName:'Ebonyi',
        MechanicName:'',
        MechanicNumber:'0913608965',
      },
      {
        SN:'ED',
        StateName:'Edo',
        MechanicName:'',
        MechanicNumber:'0913608965',
      },
      {
        SN:'EK',
        StateName:'Ekiti',
        MechanicName:'',
        MechanicNumber:'0913608965',
      },
      {
        SN:'EN',
        StateName:'Enugu',
        MechanicName:'',
        MechanicNumber:'0913608965',
      },
      {
        SN:'GO',
        StateName:'Gombe',
        MechanicName:'',
        MechanicNumber:'0913608965',
      },
      {
        SN:'IM',
        StateName:'Imo',
        MechanicName:'',
        MechanicNumber:'0913608965',
      },
      {
        SN:'JI',
        StateName:'Jigawa',
        MechanicName:'',
        MechanicNumber:'0913608965',
      },
      {
        SN:'KD',
        StateName:'Kaduna',
        MechanicName:'',
        MechanicNumber:'0913608965',
      },
      {
        SN:'KN',
        StateName:'Kano',
        MechanicName:'',
        MechanicNumber:'0913608965',
      },
      {
        SN:'KT',
        StateName:'Katsina',
        MechanicName:'',
        MechanicNumber:'0913608965',
      },
      {
        SN:'KE',
        StateName:'Kebbi',
        MechanicName:'',
        MechanicNumber:'0913608965',
      },
      {
        SN:'KO',
        StateName:'Kogi',
        MechanicName:'',
        MechanicNumber:'0913608965',
      },
      {
        SN:'KW',
        StateName:'Kwara',
        MechanicName:'',
        MechanicNumber:'0913608965',
      },
      {
        SN:'LA',
        StateName:'Lagos',
        MechanicName:'',
        MechanicNumber:'0913608965',
      },
      {
        SN:'NA',
        StateName:'Nassarawa',
        MechanicName:'',
        MechanicNumber:'0913608965',
      },
      {
        SN:'NI',
        StateName:'Niger',
        MechanicName:'',
        MechanicNumber:'0913608965',
      },
      {
        SN:'OG',
        StateName:'Ogun',
        MechanicName:'',
        MechanicNumber:'0913608965',
      },
      {
        SN:'ON',
        StateName:'Ondo',
        MechanicName:'',
        MechanicNumber:'0913608965',
      },
      {
        SN:'OS',
        StateName:'Osun',
        MechanicName:'',
        MechanicNumber:'0913608965',
      },
      {
        SN:'OY',
        StateName:'Oyo',
        MechanicName:'',
        MechanicNumber:'0913608965',
      },
      {
        SN:'PL',
        StateName:'Plateau',
        MechanicName:'',
        MechanicNumber:'0913608965',
      },
      {
        SN:'RI',
        StateName:'Rivers',
        MechanicName:'',
        MechanicNumber:'0913608965',
      },
      {
        SN:'SO',
        StateName:'Sokoto',
        MechanicName:'',
        MechanicNumber:'0913608965',
      },
      {
        SN:'TA',
        StateName:'Taraba',
        MechanicName:'',
        MechanicNumber:'0913608965',
      },
      {
        SN:'YO',
        StateName:'Yobe',
        MechanicName:'',
        MechanicNumber:'0913608965',
      },
      {
        SN:'ZA',
        StateName:'Zamfara',
        MechanicName:'',
        MechanicNumber:'0913608965',
      },
    ]